Guide to the Office of Sponsored Research records, 1942-1996 RG0038
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Government contract projects, 1951-1958; RG0038 Series 1; 11 Linear feet
  - Naval Air Station: San Diego Fleet Aviation Accounting Office, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Pacific
  - Fleet Activities: Sasebo, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Naval Station: Subic Bay, Philippine Islands, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Fleet Activities: Yokosuka, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan: Research Papers, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Data Disposal, 06/1957 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Data Disposal, 08/1957 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Progress Report: J.E. Hamilton, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Material Classes, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Not Edited
  - Korean Data Collection Plan: Research Papers, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan: Research Papers, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - PaperWork Afloat, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Admission Cases, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Applications for Positions, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - "A" Miscellaneous Budget, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Budget: Early Drafts, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Bureau Project, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - "B" Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Coker, Joseph D.: Correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Restricted
  - Commerce, Department of, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Communication Requisition, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Construction Statistics, Division Of, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Bureau of Labor Statistics
  - Consultant Statements, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Contract, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Corp of Engineers, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Defense Electric Power Administration, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Directorate of Intelligence: The Air Targets Division, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Ebasco Services, Inc, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Edison Electric Institute, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Equipment Requisitions, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - "E" Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Federal Power commission, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - "F" Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - General Electric Company, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - "G" Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - TGWU: Interdepartmental Memorandums, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - International Trade, Office of, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Deparment of Commerce
  - I Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Kossack, Carl F Correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Labor Statistics, Bureau of, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Letters of Clearance, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Letters of Introduction, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Liquidations, Division of, Department of Commerce, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Log Contract Year, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Log Fourth Quarter, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    July-September
  - Log Third Quarter, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    April-June
  - Log Second Quarter, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Jan-March
  - L Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Marshall and Stevens, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Chicago 4, Illinois, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - E. Jayer: USAF, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Morrison-Knudsen Company, Inc: The EM-KAYAN, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - M Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - McCrossin Correspondences, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - National Production Authority, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - N Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Personnel: 32 Individual folders, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Personnel, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Mr Youssef B. Rakha, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - RAND Corporation, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Reclamation, Bureau of, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Divider: Request for Access to Information, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - "R" Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Salary, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Security, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Sixth Monthly Report, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - John W. Skinner, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Statement of Pilot Project, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Stone and Webster Engineering Corporation, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Supply Requisitions, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - "S" Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - TVA: Knoxville, undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Travel Statements and Requisitions, undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Dr Watson: Personnel, undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Whitman Reguardt and Associates, undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - "W" Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Yeager, Leland B., undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
    Correspondence
  - PVT Arnold Zellner, undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - The Air Targets Division, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Bell, Gordon E., undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Boilers, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Classification of Hydro Power Projects, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cokor Training Proposal, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Commerce, Deparment of, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Component Damage and Repair: Insurance form 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Norton
  - Components of Hydro and Steam Plants, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Divider: Construction Costs, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Construction and Reconstruction Data, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Appalachia TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    TR 5, Volume 2
  - The Chatuge Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - The Cherokee Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    TR 7
  - The Chickamauga Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
    TR 6
  - Douglas Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Electra Project: Hydro 137, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Fontana Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    TR 12
  - The Fort Loudon Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
    TR 11
  - The Gunterville Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
    TR 4
  - The Hiwassee Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    TR 5, Volume 1
  - The Hiwassee Valley Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Kentucky Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Norris Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    TR 1
  - The Nottely Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Ocoee 3 TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
    TR 5, Volume2
  - Pickwick Landing Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - The Watts Bar Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - The Watts Bar Steam Plant TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
    TR 8
  - West Point Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Construction Cost Comparisons over Time Price Chager: Connecticut Stewart, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Construction Scheduling in Hydroelectric Projects: JW Skinner, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Coogan, James F., undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Divider: Cost Analysis, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - The Cherokee Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Chickamauga Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Douglas Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Electra, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - The Fontana Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Fort Laudon Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - The Gunterville Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - The Hiwassee Report, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Kentucky Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - The Norris Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Pickwick Landing Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Toketee: Licensed Plant, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - The Wheeler Project, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Security Forms, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Consultant Statement Forms, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Travel Forms, undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - The Wheeler Project TVA, undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
    TR 2
  - Damage and Rehabilitation Experience in the Electric Power Industry: Robert E. Johnson, undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Divider: Data Book, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
    See also Foreign Hydro Plants Data Book, Section III
  - Electrical Equipment Data Book: Section I, undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Hydro Turbines and Generators Data Book: Section I, undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Steam Plant Equipment Data Book: Section I, undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Cost Data Data Book: Section II, undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Defense Electric Power Administration, undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Rafael Deharo Reports, undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Edison Electric Institute, undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Electric Power Industry: Recuperability in Report, undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
    Coogan and Manne
  - Electric Power Industry: Recuperability in, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
    Boilers and Transformers by Leland B. Yeager
  - Electric Power Industry: Recuperability in Basic Data, undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Electric World, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Electrical Equipment: Productive Capacity, undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Divider: Electric Power Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Possible Method of Analyzing Recuperability in Significant Industries, undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
    Dr. Paul Johnstone and James Hibbs
  - Appalachian Electric Power Company: Cabin Creek, West Virginia, undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Appalachian Electric Power Company: Logan, West Virginia, undated (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Arkansas Inspection and Rating Bureau: Little Rock, Arkansas, undated (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Bangor Hydro-Electric Company: Bangor, Maine, undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Block Island Power and Light Company: Block Island, Rhode Island, undated (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Brockton Edison Company: East Bridgewater, Massachussetts, undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Boston Edison Company: Boston, Massachussetts, undated (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Brooklyn Edison Company: Brooklyn, New York, undated (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - The California Oregon Power Company: Medford, Oregon, undated (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Central Vermont Public Service Company: Rutland, Vermont, undated (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Center Maine Power Company: Augusta, Maine, undated (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - City Council: Dyersburg, Tennessee, undated (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Consolidated Gas Electric Light and Power Company of Baltimore: Baltimore, MD, undated (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - The Connecticut Light and Power Company: Waterbury, Connecticut, undated (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Connecticut Power and Light Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Dayton Power and Light Company: Dayton, Ohio, undated (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Defense Production Act: Electric Power Study, undated (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Diesel Electric Plant: Deshler, Ohio, undated (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Reconstruction Sources of Data Factory: Mutual Engineering Division, undated (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Florida Power and Light Company: Miami FL, undated (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Hartford Electric Light: Hartford 15, Connecticut, undated (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - The Home Insurance Company: 59 Maiden Lane, New York, New York, undated (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Indianapolis Power and Light Company: Indianapolis, Indiana, undated (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Kansas Gas and Electric Company: Wichita, Kansas, undated (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Kansas Power and Light Company: Topeka, Kansas, undated (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Lehigh Portland Cement Company: Allentown, Pennsylvania, undated (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Lousiana-Southwest Gas and Electric Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Lumbermens Mutual Casaulty Company: Chicago 40, Illinois, undated (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Lynn Gas and Electric Company: West Lynn, Massachussetts, undated (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Maine and Cumberland Connecticut: Y P+L, undated (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Massachussets, Boston: Edison, undated (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Massachussetts, Malden and Melrose GL Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Massachussetts, New England Power SV Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority: Boston, Massachussetts, undated (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Montaup Electric Company: Sommerset, Massachussetts, undated (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Municipal Light and Power Plant: Readstown, Wisconsin, undated (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Reconstruction Sources of Data: Mutual Boiler Insurance Company of Boston, undated (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Narragansett Electric Company: Providence, Rhode Island, undated (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - New Hampshire and New England Power, undated (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Massachussetts, Holyoke Water Power Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - New Hampshire and New England Gas and Electric Association, undated (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - New Hampshire Electric Company: Portsmouth, New Hampshire, undated (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - New Mexico Power and Light Company: White Oaks, New Mexico, undated (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation: Syracuse, New York, undated (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - New Orleans Public Service Inc: New Orleans, Louisiana, undated (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Northern States Power Company: Minneapolis, Minnesota, undated (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Northwestern Light and Power Company: Spirit Lake, Iowa, undated (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Ohio Edison Company: Akron, Ohio, undated (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Oklahoma Gas and Electric Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Public Service Company of Colorado: Denver, Colorado, undated (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Pacific Gas and Electric Company: St Albans, Vermont, undated (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Power Service Company of Indiana Inc: Plainfield, Indiana, undated (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Public Service Company of New Hampshire, undated (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Public Service Gas and Electric Company: Newark, New Jersey, undated (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Rhode Island, Blackstone Valley Gas and Electric Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Rhode Island, Rhode Island Public Service Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Southwestern Gas and Electric Company: Shreveport, Louisiana, undated (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Vermont, Central Vermont Public Service Corporation, undated (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Western Mass Electric Company: Greenfield, Massachussetts, undated (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - West Virginia, undated (Box 7, Folder 126)
    Various
  - Western Massachusetts Electric Company: Buckland, Massachussetts, undated (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Wisconsin Public Service Company: Greenbay, Wisconsin, undated (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Facilities Protection Department of Commerce, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Federal Power Commission, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Divider- Material Classified by Countries, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Africa, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Alaska, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Australia, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Austria, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Belgium, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Brazil, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Canada, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Central America, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - China, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Egypt, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - England, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Europe, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Finland, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - France, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Germany, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Greece, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Hungary, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - India, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Italy, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Japan, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Latin America Hydro Projects, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Mexico, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - New Zealand, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Philippine Islands, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Portugal, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Russia: General, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Russia [1/2], undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Russia [2/2], undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Scandinavia, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Siam, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Spain, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - South America, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Switzerland, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Turkey, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Divider: Report Classified by Continents, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Africa, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Asia, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Australia, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Europe, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Latin America, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - North America, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Foreign Periodicals, List of, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Foreign: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Foreign Hydro Plants: Drafts, undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Divider:Form one, undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Form one: Licensed Plants [1/2], undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Form one: Licensed Plants [2/2], undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Form one: Reclamation, Bureau of, undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Form Two, undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Form One: TVA Projects, undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Generators, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Divider: Hydro Report, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Hydro Projects: General, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Hydro Report: Second Draft of Chapter I, undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Chapter I: Materials, undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Time Carbons, undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Charts and Tables: Originals, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Time, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Hydro Report: Second Draft of Chapter II, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Chapter II Materials
  - Hydro Report: Second Draft of Chapter III, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Chapter III Materials
  - Hydro Report: Second Draft of Chapter IV, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Chapter IV Materials
  - Hydro Report: Second Draft of Chapter V, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Chapter V Materials
  - Hydro Report: Second Draft of Chapter V, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Hydro Report: Second Draft of Chapter VI, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Chapter VI Materials
  - Hydro Report: Second Draft of Chapter VII, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Chapter VII: Materials, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Hydro Report: Appendix, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Appendix, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Imput Data, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Divider: Insurance, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Installation of Additional Units: M.L. Loe, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Insurance companies: Inactive, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Insurance Companies: Active, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Insurance: Correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Casualty Bureaus Receiving Form Letter, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Insurance Data on Rehabilitation, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Insurance Data Summary: Mr Otto, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Local Rating Bureaus, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - The Locomotive Hartford Steam Boiler Insurance Company, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - National Board of Fire Underwriters, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Sources of Data in the Insurance Field: IHE Otto, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Southeastern Underwriters Association, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Alabama, South Carolina, Virgina, Florida, and North Carolina
  - Travelers Insurance Company, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Insurance: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Investment Planning in the Electric Utility Industry: GWU, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Mr Welshans
  - Johnson, E.H., undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Kossack, Carl F., undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Materials and Questionnaires
  - Labor Department: Dan Project, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Labor Required in Equipment Manufacture, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - List of Hydro Plants: Robert L. Taylor, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Loe, M.L., undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Myron L. Loe, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Logistics Conference, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Machine Tools, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Manufacturers of Electrical Equipment: Foreign, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    G. Bell
  - Materials Used in Construction of Power Plants: WPB, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Methods and Procedures, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Munitions Board: Department of Defense, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mutual Security Agency, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - McCall Reports, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - McCrossin Materials, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - National Production Authority, Department of Commerce, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - H.S. Norton's Reports, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - In Golf HE Otto, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Outline, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Railroad Management Research Project, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Reclamation, Bureau of: Power Pamphlets, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Reclamation, Bureau of: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Redeveloped Plants, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Salveson, Melvin E., undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Skinner, John W., undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Steam Generator Plants, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Statistical Survey of Economic Factors Relevant to Construction
  - Steam Plants [1/2], undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Steam Plants [2/2], undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Charles T. Stewart, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Divider: Planning and Scheduling Production Processes, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    See Salveson, Melvin E.
  - Plant Factor Table and Supporting Schedules, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Purdue: Materials, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Purdue: Oil Refinements, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Robert L. Taylor Reports, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - TVA, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
    General
  - Transformers, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Turbines, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Turbo Generators, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Underground Power Plants, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Utilities and Fuels Division Facilities and Service, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - A Rational Basis for Classification of Hydro-Electric Developments: Carl H Walther, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Donald S. Watson Reports, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Worcester Street Railway Company: Worcester, Massachussetts, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - World Power Conferences: M.L. Loe, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - World Power Plants by Class, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
    Volumes I and II
  - Unmarked File, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Yeager, Leland B., undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
    Reports
  - Yeager, Leland B. [1/2], undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
    Rough Drafts and Copies
  - Yeager, Leland B. [2/2], undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Bureau of Reclamation Construction Programs, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Recuperability of Electric Power Facilities, undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
    Technical Report 1
  - Construction and Reconstruction of Hydro Electric Power Plants, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
    Technical Report 2
  - Statistical Survey of the Economic Factors Relevant to Construction of Steam Generating Plants, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
    Technical Report 3
  - Recuperability of Electric Generator Manufacturing Capacity, undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
    Technical Report 4
  - Recuperability of the Transformer Industry, undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
    Technical Report 5
  - Recuperability of the Boiler Industry, undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
    Technical Report 6
- Logistics projects reports, 1950-1959; RG0038 Series 2; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of logistics technical project reports. Their arrangement is chronological by report number. The series also includes monthly progress reports, employee/salary lists, and interviews. The material dates from the 1950's and was transferred to the University Archives by the Director of Sponsored Research in 1987.